gojobs.com 2010-12-31

# GO Jobs Privacy Statement

**Privacy Statement**

**Overview**

GO Jobs is committed to respecting the privacy of our users. We strive to provide a safe, secure user experience. This Privacy Statement sets forth the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply to all of our Web sites (unless a different privacy statement is specifically made applicable). By using a GO Jobs, Inc. Web site, you consent to the policies and practices described in this Statement. 

Your data will be stored and processed in whole or in part in the United States. If you access a GO Jobs Web site outside the United States, your usage of that site constitutes consent to the transfer of your data out of your country and to the United States. 

Our sites contain links to other Web sites over which we have no control. GO Jobs is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other Web sites to which you choose to link from a GO Jobs Web site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other Web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information. This Privacy Statement applies solely to the information we collect on a GO Jobs Web site, and does not apply to information we collect in any other fashion.

**Collection and Retention of Information**

In some areas of our Web sites, GO Jobs requests or may request that you provide personal information, including your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number credit card number, social security number, contact information, billing information and any other information from which your identity is discernible. In other areas, GO Jobs collects or may collect demographic information that is not unique to you such as your ZIP code, age, preferences, gender, interests and favorites. Sometimes we collect or may collect a combination of the two types of information. Examples of areas on GO Jobs Web sites where we collect personal or combined personal and demographic data are pages where you can open a MyGOJobs account, sign up to use a service, post a resume, enter a contest or purchase a product.

We also gather or may gather certain information about your use of our site, such as what areas you visit and what services you access. Moreover, there is information about your computer hardware and software that is or may be collected by GO Jobs. This information can include without limitation your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. 

GO Jobs may sometimes afford you the opportunity to provide descriptive, cultural, behavioral, preferential and/or life style information about yourself, but it is solely up to you whether you furnish such information. If you do provide such information, you are thereby consenting to the use of that information in accordance with the policies and practices described in this Statement. For example, such information may be used for the purpose of determining your potential interest in receiving email or other communications about particular products or services. 

Since we believe that managing your career is a life-long process, we retain indefinitely all the information we gather about you in an effort to make your repeat use with us more efficient, practical, and relevant. Of course, you can correct or update your MyGOJobs account profile and resume at any time. Moreover, you can delete your resume from our online database or close your MyGOJobs account at any time, in which event we will remove all our copies of your resume and MyGOJobs account profile information except for an archival copy which is not accessible on the Internet. 

**Use of Information by GO Jobs**

We use the information we gather on a GO Jobs Web site, whether personal, demographic, collective or technical, for the purpose of operating and improving the GO Jobs Web site, fostering a positive user experience, and delivering the products and services that we offer. 

We may also use the information we gather to inform you of other products or services available from GO Jobs or its affiliated companies or to contact you about your opinion of current products and services or potential new products and services that may be offered. 

We may use your contact information in order to send you e-mail or other communications regarding updates at the GO Jobs site, such as new GO Jobs opportunities and additional listings which may be of interest to you. The nature and frequency of these messages will vary depending upon the information we have about you. In addition, at the time of registration for MyGOJobs, you have the option to elect to receive additional communications, information and promotions including without limitation free informational newsletters from GO Jobs relating to topics that may be of special interest to you, such as career management advice. 

We have an area where you can submit feedback. Any feedback you submit in this area becomes our property, and we can use such feedback (such as success stories) for marketing purposes or contact you for further information. 

**Disclosure of Information to Others**

We do not disclose to third parties your personal information, combined personal and demographic information or information about your use of a GO Jobs Web site (such as the areas you visit or the services you access), except as set forth in the following four subparagraphs. 

  1.    We may disclose such information to third parties if you consent to such disclosure. For example, if you indicate that you would like to receive information about the products or services of third parties at the time you register for a MyGOJobs account, we may supply your contact information to third parties such as employers, recruiters, data aggregators, marketers or others for the purpose of sending you e-mail or otherwise communicating with you. We may use data we have about you (such as the interests and preferences you have expressed) to determine whether you might be interested in the products or services of a particular third-party 
  2.    We may disclose such information to companies and individuals we employ to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include hosting our Web servers, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These companies and individuals will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions, but they may not share that information with any other third party. 
  3.    We may disclose such information if legally required to do so, if requested to do so by a governmental entity or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect the rights or property of GO Jobs or its affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public. 
  4.    We may disclose and transfer such information to a third party who acquires all or a substantial portion of GO Jobs's business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event GO Jobs becomes the subject of a bankruptcy proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, GO Jobs or its trustee in bankruptcy may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court. 

GO Jobs may also share aggregated anonymous information about visitors to each of its Web sites (for example, the number of visitors to GO Jobs's Diversity area) with its clients, partners and other third parties so that they may understand the kinds of visitors to GO Jobs's site and how those visitors use the site. 

GO Jobs supplies technology, hosting and related services to other leading companies to power recruitment areas on their Web sites (sometimes referred to as "private label recruitment areas"). Personal and/or demographic information supplied by you in private label recruitment areas becomes part of the GO Jobs database, but it is not accessible by anyone other than you, GO Jobs and the company concerned without your consent. 

Information gathered on a page in a private label recruitment area, or on a co-branded page (such as that of a contest co-sponsored by GO Jobs and another company), may become the property of the other company or of both GO Jobs and the other company. In that instance, the use of such information by the other company may be subject to the privacy policy of that company and, in any event, GO Jobs is not responsible for that company's use of your personal or demographic information. 

If you apply for a position through a co-branded site, you may be asked to provide information on your age, gender or race.  Some employers are required by law to gather this information from job applicants for reporting and record keeping requirements.  You should understand that if provided, this information will be used by employers only in accordance with applicable law and will not be used in making any employment decisions.  All information provided will be kept separate from your expression of interest in any job opportunity.   Providing this information is strictly voluntary and you will not be subject to any adverse action or treatment if you choose not to provide this information. 

**Resumes**

Since GO Jobs is a career site, we give you the option of putting your resume in our database. There are two ways of doing this: 

  1. can store your resume in our database, but not allow it to be searchable by potential employers. Not allowing your resume to be searchable means that you can use it to apply for a job online, but employers and recruiters will not have access to search it through our resume database product. 
  2. If you allow your resume to be searchable, then all parties with access to our searchable resume database (or copies thereof) will have access to your resume. 

We attempt to limit access to our searchable resume database (or copies thereof) only to paying employers, recruiters, hiring managers, headhunters, and human resource professionals, as well as law enforcement and national security agencies, but cannot guarantee that other parties will not gain access to this database. We are not responsible for the use made of resumes by third parties who access such resumes while they are in our searchable database. You may remove your resume from our searchable database at any time. However, employers, recruiters and others who have paid for access to that database or to obtain a copy of that database, as well as parties who have otherwise gained access to the database, may have retained a copy of your resume in their own files or databases. We are not responsible for the retention, use or privacy of resumes in these instances. 

**Use of Cookies**

GO Jobs uses "cookies" to help personalize and maximize your online experience and time online. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard drive by a Web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize GO Jobs pages, or register for services, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information (such as user name, password and preferences). Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster and more accurate results and a more personalized site experience. When you return to the GO Jobs site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customized. We also use cookies to track click streams and for load balancing. 

You may have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline all cookies if you prefer. Alternatively, you may be able to modify your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis. If you choose to decline cookies, however, that may hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on the GO Jobs Web site. 

**Updating Your Information**

You may review, correct, update or change your MyGOJobs account profile information at any time. Simply log into your MyGOJobs account, go to your Account Profile, review your account information and, if you wish, edit it with the options provided. [Click here](http://www.gojobs.com/) to access your Account Profile page. 

If you opted to receive newsletters, commercial e-mails or other communications from GO Jobs or third parties at the time you registered with MyGOJobs, but subsequently change your mind, you may opt-out by editing your Account Profile as described above. If you previously opted not to receive such communications, you may later opt-in by editing your Account Profile. . 

**Security**

GO Jobs has implemented reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. 

When you place an order online at GO Jobs, your credit card information is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") protocol. SSL makes it difficult for your credit card information to be intercepted or stolen while being transmitted. GO Jobs uses a service company to process its credit card transactions. 

**Children**

GO Jobs is not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. 

**Changes to Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our Privacy Statement for GO Jobs, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it. If at any time, you have questions or concerns about GO Jobs's Privacy Statement, please feel free to email us at gojobs@gojobs.com or call us at 1-949-838-0055 and speak to one of our representatives. 

**Contact Information**

GO Jobs, Inc., a California corporation, with its principal place of business at 4500 Campus Drive, Suite 420 Newport Beach, CA 92660, is the legal entity, which determines the purposes and means of processing the information gathered at the GO Jobs Web sites. The information we gather on any GO Jobs Web site may be shared within GO Jobs, Inc. and its affiliated companies. 

We welcome your comments concerning this Privacy Statement. If you believe that we have not adhered to this Statement, please contact us by e-mailing us at 

GoJobs @ gojobs.com  or by calling us at 1-714-771-1714. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem. 

Thank you for using GOJobs.com.
